A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 2 FA1390
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 2
1928-2004
Rockefeller Archive Center
China Medical Board (U.S.)
FA1390
43.03 Cubic Feet 88 legal document boxes, 2 letter document boxes, 1 flat file
Scope and Contents
Type of records include: Reports, publications, newspaper articles, correspondence, reprints, architectural drawing, photographs, video tapes. The Finance Committee Files includes documentation for the Cox & Reece Hearings.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
These records are in four series, 1. Grants and Subject Files, 2. Members and Officer Files, 3. Finance Committee Files, and 4. Audiovisual Materials
- Grants and Subject Files, 1964-1967, 1969, 1971-2004; 1; 23.91 Cubic Feet 49 legal document boxes and 1 flat file
  - 81-398, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1981-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 82-408, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1982-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 83-418, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1983-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 85-435, Beijing Medical College, Supplemental Endowment for Staff Development, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 86-443, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Nursing Education, 1986, 1988-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 86-446, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Postgraduate Training, 1986, 1988-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 86-449, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Public Health, 1986, 1988-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 87-468, Beijing Medical University, Endowment Fund for Technical Training and Administrative Personnel, 1987-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 88-480, Beijing Medical University, Fund for General Institutional Development, 1988-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 88-503, Beijing Medical University, Li, Rui, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 88-505, Beijing Medical University, Biomedical Research, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 89-519, Beijing Medical University, Cancer Research Program, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 90-523, Beijing Medical University, Interdisciplinary Program/Immunology, 1990-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 90-533, Beijing Medical University-Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), Fellowship Program, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 92-555, Beijing Medical University, Program in Medical Ethics, 1991-1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 92-560, Beijing Medical University, Supplemental Staff Development, 1992, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 93-591, Beijing Medical University, Vascular Medicine, 1992-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 94-603, Beijing Medical University, General Institution Development, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 96-653, Beijing Medical University, Non-Insulin Dependents Diabetes Mellitus (NIDDM), 1996-2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 95-615, Peking University Health Science Center (Beijing Medical University), Cancer Research, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 96-628, Peking University Health Science Center (Beijing Medical University), H-Pylori, 1996-2002 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 96-652, Peking University Health Science Center (Beijing Medical University), Association of Medical Universities and Colleges in China (AMUCC), 1996-2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 88-503, Zhejiang Medical University, CD-ROM, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 89-000, Zhejiang Medical University, FAX Machine, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 89-515, Zhejiang Medical University, Social Medicine, 1989-1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fellowships, Statistics and General Information, China Medical Board-Fellows, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fellowships, Statistics and General Information, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Program Evaluation Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - 92-580, University of Health Services, Sound System for Amphitheater, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 93-592, China Medical University, Poison Control and Information Center, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences, 1979, 1983-1988, 1990, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - West China University of Medical Sciences, New York State Charter Reinstatement, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 92-558, West China University of Medical Sciences, Clinical Microbiology and Infectious Diseases, 1992-1999 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 92-571, West China University of Medical Sciences, Clinical Laboratory Medicine, 1992-1999 (Box 4, Folder 35, Folder 1)
  - 93-585, West China University of Medical Sciences, Reform of Medical Education, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 93-596, West China University of Medical Sciences, Community-Based Gerontology, 1993, 1995-1999, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 95-622, West China University of Medical Sciences, Nursing Text Books, 1995-2000 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - 96-636, West China University of Medical Sciences, General Institutional Development, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Chulalongkorn University, Dean, General Correspondence, 1973, 1980-1982, 1987, 1989, 1992-1993, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Chulalongkorn University, President, Suwanwela, Charas, 1989-1991, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, General Information, 1990-1991, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, General information, 1990-1991, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, Background Information, Establishment of College of Public Health, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 84-434, Chulalongkorn University, Endowment Fund for Faculty Development and Medical Education, Faculty of Medicine, 1981-1982, 1984-1995, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 85-435, Chulalongkorn University, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985-1989, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - 85-441, Chulalongkorn University, Endowment for Scholar Development, Faculty of Medicine, 1985-1995, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - 91-538, Chulalongkorn University, Public Health Administration, 1991-1998 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 92-579, Chulalongkorn University, College of Public Health, Implementation of Workshop on Problem Solving for Better Health, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 99-715, Chulalongkorn University, Faculty of Medicine, Quality Improvement Model, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Mahidol University, General Information, 1987-1993, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Mahidol University-Siriraj Hospital, General Correspondence, Dean & Faculty Members, 1979, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Mahidol University, Siriraj Faculty of Nursing, General Correspondence, Dean, 1984, 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 76-358, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1973, 1976-1990, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 77-362, Madihol University, Faculty of Nursing, Nursing Education, Training, & Research, 1976-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - 78-376, Madihol University, Siriraj Hospital, Library Endowment, 1978-1989, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 79-379, Madihol University, Siriraj Hospital, Faculty of Medicine, Scholar Development Project, 1978-1995 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 80-396, Madihol University, Faculty of Nursing, endowment for Nursing Education, 1980-1994 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - 83-427, Madihol University, Siriraj Hospital, faculty of Medicine, Endowment for General Development, 1983-1990, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - 85-435, Madihol University, Siriraj Hospital, Faculty of Medicine, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985-1989, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - 85-437, Madihol University, Faculty of Public Health, Public Health Programs, 1985, 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - 87-479, Madihol University, Faculty of Nursing, Supplemental Endowment for Staff Development, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - 89-509, Madihol University, Faculty of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Preclinical Departments, 1989-1990, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - 89-510, Madihol University, Endowment Fund, Medical Scholars Program, 1989-1997 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - 89-511, Madihol University, Integrated Program on Cancer, 1989-1997 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - 89-511, Madihol University, Integrated Program on Cancer, Publications (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - 89-512, Madihol University, Biomedical Instrumentation, 1989-1997 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - 81-404-2, 81-404-5, 81-414-1, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Fellowships, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - 83-417, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Production of Video Tapes, 1985-1988, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - 84-428, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1984-1994, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - 84-429, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1984-1994, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - 84-430, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1984-1998 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - 85-435, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Supplemental Endowment-Staff Development, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - 86-453-1, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Faculty of Medicine, 1986, 1988-1998 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - 86-435-2, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Faculty of Public Health, 1986, 1988-1990, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - 86-453-3, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Department of Nursing, 1986, 1988-1991, 1994, 1996, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - 87-472, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for Training Technical Personnel, 1987-1998 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - 88-485, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Endowment Fund for General Institutional Development, 1988-1998 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - 88-507, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Biomedical Research, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - 90-529, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Nasopharyngeal Cancer Program, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - 90-532, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Audio-Visual Teaching Material, 1989-1997 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - 90-534, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Fellowship Program, 1990-1996 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - 91-548, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Environmental & Occupational Health, 1991-1997, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - 91-549, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Behavioral Medicine, 1991-1999 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - 92-565, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Supplemental Medical Research, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - 92-569, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Genetic Counseling Network, 1992-1997, 1999, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - 93-594, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Fellowship Program, 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - 93-595, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences/University of Singapore, Environmental and Occupational Health, 1993-1999, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - 94-606, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, General Institutional Development, 1994, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Tongji University, General Correspondence, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Chinese Medical Association, Zeyi, Cao, Executive Vice President, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - 62-626, University of Singapore, Visiting Professor, McKelvey, John L., 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - 67-962, University of Singapore, Visiting Professor, McKelvey, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1964-1965, 1967-1968, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - 85-435, National University of Singapore, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - 85-436, National University of Singapore, Fellowships and Medical Education, Department of Social Medicine-Public Health, 1985-1997 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Meeting No. 1, General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Lancaster Update, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - CONGE, University of Texas, Houston, Starck, Patricia, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - CONGE, University of Texas, Houston, Starck, Patricia, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 98A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restrictedl-Personal information
  - CONGE, University of Texas, Houston, Starck, Patricia and Sherwood, Gwen, 1989-1990, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, General Correspondence, 1988-1993, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 100-101)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, General Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1986, 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Beijing Medical University, Applications, 1989, 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, China Medical University, Applications, 1989, 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Hunan Medical University, Applications, 1989, 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Peking Union Medical College, Applications, 1989, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Shanghai Medical University, Applications, 1989, 1988-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Sun Yat-Sen University of Medical Sciences, Applications, 1989, 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, West China University of Medical Sciences, Applications, 1989, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - CONGE, Nursing Education, Xi'an Medical University, Applications, 1989, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - CONGE, Consortium of American Schools of Nursing for Nursing Education in China, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - CONGE, Catholic University of America, Flaherty, Mary Jean, 1989-1992, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - CONGE, George Mason University, Carthy, Rita and Rudowski, Lorainne, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - CONGE, University of California, San Francisco, Martinson, Ida, 1989-1992, 1994, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - CONGE, University of Tennessee, Memphis, Carter, Michael, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - CONGE, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Lancaster, Jeanette, 1989-1996 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - 81-397, CONGE, China Trip, Lancaster, Jeanette and Starck, Patricia, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - 90-528, Shanghai Medical University, Hand and Microvascular Surgery Program, 1990-1997 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - 91-545, Shanghai Medical University, Health Management, 1991-1998 (Box 15, Folder 119-121)
  - 92-561, Shanghai Medical University, Supplemental Staff Development, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - 80-384, Co-Operative Planning Development, PRC Dean's Travel to Medical Schools in Southeast Asia, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - 80-384, Co-Operative Planning Development, Medical Library Seminar, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 124-125)
  - 80-384, Co-Operative Planning Development, Seoul National University, International Workshop on Evaluation of Postgraduate Pediatric Education, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - 80-384, Co-Operative Planning Development, Medical Research Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - 80-384, Co-Operative Planning Development, Medical Education Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - 80-384, 83-417, Co-Operative Planning Development, Audiovisual Techniques, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - 80-384, Co-Operative Planning Development, China Medical Board (CMB)-Asia Society Meeting, Speakers, 1981-1982, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - 81-397, Bureau of Public Health of Tibet, Fax Machine, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - 98-694, Tibet Medical College, Supplement to Grant 68-679, 1998-2003 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - 92-568, Hunan Medical University, Etho-Pharmacology, 1991-1999 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - 96-648, Xiangya School of Medicine, Substance Abuse, 1995-2003 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - 96-656, Xiangya School of Medicine, Suicide Prevention, 1996-2003 (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - 98-689, Xiangya School of Medicine, Disease Prevention after Floods, 1998-2003 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - 79-383, Chiang Mai University, Endowment Staff Development, 1979-1989, 1991, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - 80-388, Chiang Mai University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1980-1989, 1991, 1993-1994, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - 81-397, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Medicine, Sirisanthana, Thira, 1990, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - 81-406, Chiang Mai University, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1981-1996 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - 84-432, Chiang Mai University, Endowment Fund for General Development, 1983-1996 (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - 85-435, Chiang Mai University, Supplemental Endowment for Staff Development, 1985-1992 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - 87-475, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Medicine, Endowment Fund for General Development, 1987-1989, 1991-1993, 1995-1997. 1999 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - 87-476, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Endowment for Staff Development, 1987-1989, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - 88-503, Chiang Mai University, Consortium of Thai Medical Schools, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - 88-503, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Gerontology Program, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - 89-508, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Infection Control Nursing, 1989-1997 (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - 92-567, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Program in Home Care Nursing, 1992-1997 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - 92-579, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Implementation of Workshop on Problem Solving for Better Health, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - 93-590, Chiang Mai University, Faculty of Nursing, Geriatric Nursing, 1993-1999 (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - 95-613, Chiang Mai University, Medical Education, 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - National Taiwan University, General Correspondence, Dean and Staff, 1973, 1976, 1982-1988, 1990-1991, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - 85-440, National Taiwan University, College of Medicine, Training of Technical, Nursing and Administration Personnel, 1985-1995 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - 88-503, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Nursing Conversion Degree Program, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - University of Singapore, General Correspondence, Dean, 1973-1974, 1983, 1987-1989, 1993, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - 76-351, University of Singapore, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1976, 1978-1979, 1983-1997 (Box 19, Folder 157)
  - Seoul National University, College of Medicine/Nursing, General Correspondence, 1972-1973, 1976-1977, 1980, 1984-1986, 1989-1990, 1992-1993, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 158)
  - Seoul National University, College of Nursing, 90th Anniversary Celebration, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 159)
  - 77-360, Yonsei University, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - 77-363, University of Indonesia, Faculty of Public Health, Paramedical Education and Research, 1977-1978, 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - 84-433, University of Indonesia, Faculty of Public Health, Training of Paramedical Personnel, 1984-1994 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - 88-503, University of Indonesia, Faculty of Public Health, Public Health Consultants, 1992 January 27-29, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - 92-577, University of Indonesia, Urban Health Care, 1992-1998 (Box 20, Folder 164-165)
  - 92-579, University of Indonesia, Implementation of Workshop on Problem Solving for Better Health, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - Indonesia, Medicine, Dean and Staff, General Correspondence, 1971-1973, 1977, 1979, 1981, 1983-1985, 1987-1990, 1992-1999 (Box 20, Folder 167-168)
  - University of Indonesia, Public Health, Dean and Staff, General Correspondence, 1972-1978, 1980, 1982-1995, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  - Hasanuddin University, Faculty of Public Health, General, Legal Opinion Letter, 1992-1998 (Box 20, Folder 170)
  - 92-576, Hasanuddin University, Faculty of Public Health, Public Health Education, 1992-1998 (Box 21, Folder 171)
  - 92-579, Hasanuddin University, Implementation of Problem Solving, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 172)
  - Airlangga University, Faculty of Medicine, Dean and Staff, General Correspondence, 1973, 1979, 1983, 1987-1988, 1990-1998 (Box 21, Folder 173)
  - 79-377, Airlangga University, Faculty Training, Research Planning, and Medical Education, 1979-1981, 1983-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 174)
  - 88-503, Airlangga University, USA Visit, Tropical Disease Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 175)
  - 90-525, Airlangga University, Community Medicine Teaching Program (CMTP), 1990, 1992-1998 (Box 21, Folder 176)
  - 91-536, Airlangga University, Tropical Disease Center (TDC), 1990-1998 (Box 22, Folder 177-178)
  - 92-579. Airlangga University, Faculty of Medicine, Problem Solving for Better Health, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 179)
  - 93-582, Medical Center of Fudan University, Hepatitis Viruses (Box 22, Folder 180)
  - 95-619, Medical Center of Fudan University, Hand and Microvascular Surgery, 1995-1997, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 181)
  - 83-417, National Teacher Training Center for Health Personnel-Seoul National University, International Education Seminar, 1985 June 19-21, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 182)
  - 83-417, Co-Operative Planning, Dean's Seminar, Zeyi, Cao, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 183)
  - University of the Philippines, College of Medicine, Dean, General Correspondence, 1973, 1979-1980, 1982-1987, 1990-1992, 1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 184)
  - 79-380, University of Hong Kong, Library Endowment Fund, 1979-1990, 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 185-186)
  - 82-415, University of Hong Kong, Regional Fellowship Program, 1981-1989, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 187)
  - 84-431, University of Hong Kong, Fellowship/PRC Nurses, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 188)
  - 85-435, University of Hong Kong, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985, 1987-1988, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 189)
  - 87-477, University of Hong Kong, Supplemental Endowment for Medical Research, 1987-1988, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 190)
  - 87-478, University of Hong Kong, Regional Fellowship Program, 1987-1992, 1994-1996, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 191)
  - 81-403, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment for Staff Development, 1981-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 23, Folder 192)
  - 82-413, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1982-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 193)
  - 82-423, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1982-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - 85-435, Xi'an Medical University, Supplemental Endowment, Staff Development, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 195)
  - 86-457, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment Fund For Nursing Education Development, 1986, 1988-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 196)
  - 86-461, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment Fund Postgraduate Medical Education Development, 1986, 1988-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 197)
  - 86-465, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment Fund for Public Health Development, 1986-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 198)
  - 87-474, Xi'an Medical University, Endowment Fund for Training Technical and Administrative Personnel, 1987-1999 (Box 24, Folder 199)
  - 88-487, Xi'an Medical University, General Institutional Development, 1988-1989, 1991-1999 (Box 25, Folder 200)
  - 89-514, Xi'an Medical University, Maternal and Child Health, 1989-1998 (Box 25, Folder 201)
  - 89-517, Xi'an Medical University, Biomedical Research, 1989, 1991-1997 (Box 25, Folder 202)
  - 90-530, Xi'an Medical University, Interdisciplinary Program on Environment, Related Bone and Teeth Disorders, 1990-1999, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 203)